Can an artist change China?
Ai Weiwei: Never Sorry is a documentary film directed by Alison Klayman.
An account of the many tribulations that Chinese artist Ai Weiwei, known for his subversive art and political activism, endured between 2008 and 2011, from his
rise to world fame via the Internet to his highly publicized arrest due to his frequent and daring confrontations with the Chinese authorities.
Self - Artist, played by Ai Weiwei.
Self - Artist, played by Chen Danqing.
Self - Sculptor, played by Li Zhanyang.
Self - Magazine Publisher, played by Hung Huang.
Self - Art Gallerist, played by Ethan Cohen.
Self - UCCA Museum Director, played by Phil Tinari.
Ai Weiwei: Never Sorry (in Chinese 艾未未：道歉你妹; official title in Taiwan 艾未未：草泥馬) is a 2012 documentary film
about Chinese artist and activist Ai Weiwei, directed by American filmmaker Alison Klayman.
Director Klayman received a special jury prize at the 2012 Sundance Film Festival for the film, which also
opened the Hot Docs Canadian International Documentary Festival in Toronto on 26 April 2012.
The film explores themes of freedom of speech, earthquake,
social activism, dissident, contemporary art.
The tone is lighthearted.